[
    {
        "question": "They say he has ________ money.",
        "options": [" A. a lot of ", " B. plenty ", " C. lots ", " D. many "],
        "answer": " A. a lot of "
    },
    {
        "question": "________ you got a high speed internet at home?",
        "options": [" A. have ", " B. are ", " C. do ", " D. has "],
        "answer": " C. do "
    },
    {
        "question": "You shall have some ice-cream when you ________ your dinner.",
        "options": [" A. finished ", " B. finish ", " C. will finish ", " D. will be finished "],
        "answer": " B. finish "
    },
    {
        "question": "At what time ________?",
        "options": [" A. does the lesson start ", " B. starts the lesson ", " C. the lesson starts ", " D. starting the lesson "],
        "answer": " A. does the lesson start "
    },
    {
        "question": "Do not get ________ the bus when it is still moving.",
        "options": [" A. of ", " B. off ", " C. out ", " D. from "],
        "answer": " B. off "
    },
    {
        "question": "The children wake ________ early in the summer.",
        "options": [" A. off ", " B. to ", " C. up ", " D. out "],
        "answer": " C. up "
    },
    {
        "question": "John ________ her yesterday.",
        "options": [" A. don't saw ", " B. didn't see ", " C. didn't saw ", " D. don't see "],
        "answer": " B. didn't see "
    },
    {
        "question": "A train is ________ a bus.",
        "options": [" A. more quickly ", " B. quickly ", " C. quicker than ", " D. more quick "],
        "answer": " C. quicker than "
    },
    {
        "question": "I must go to bed early because I ________ very sleepy.",
        "options": [" A. is ", " B. are ", " C. am ", " D. am not "],
        "answer": " C. am "
    },

        {
            "question": "Tell Chris ________ outside.",
            "options": [" A. not go ", " B. for not going ", " C. not going ", " D. not to go "],
            "answer": " D. not to go "
        },
        {
            "question": "I remember ________ him in London.",
            "options": [" A. of meeting ", " B. to meet ", " C. to meeting ", " D. meeting "],
            "answer": " D. meeting "
        },
        {
            "question": "The committee held a ________ last week.",
            "options": [" A. meeting ", " B. gathering ", " C. session ", " D. sitting "],
            "answer": " A. meeting "
        },
        {
            "question": "We wondered who was going to pay for the ________ window.",
            "options": [" A. broken ", " B. breaking ", " C. broke ", " D. break "],
            "answer": " A. broken "
        },
        {
            "question": "He died ________ hunger and cold.",
            "options": [" A. by ", " B. of ", " C. with ", " D. for "],
            "answer": " B. of "
        },
        {
            "question": "Girl: Good news. My mother let me ________ at school until five today.<br>Boy: That's good. We can study for our test together.",
            "options": [" a. stay ", " b. stayed ", " C. to stay "],
            "answer": " a. stay "
        },
        {
            "question": "Man: This is great picture.<br>Woman: Yes, it is.",
            "options": [" a. a ", " b. the ", " C. some "],
            "answer": " b. the "
        },
        {
            "question": "Man: Is this David's phone?<br>Woman: Yes, it is ________ phone?",
            "options": [" a. him ", " b. his ", " C. he "],
            "answer": " b. his "
        },
        {
            "question": "Woman: Do you live with your parents?<br>Man: No, I live by ________.",
            "options": [" a. on my own ", " b. me ", " C. myself "],
            "answer": " a. on my own "
        },
        {
            "question": "Server: Would you like ________ dessert?<br>Customer: No, thank you. I'm full.",
            "options": [" a. some ", " b. a ", " c. any "],
            "answer": " a. some "
        },
            {
                "question": "Woman: Can I borrow a pen?<br>Man: Sorry! I ________ one.",
                "options": [" a. can't ", " b. won't ", " c. don't ", " d. didn't "],
                "answer": " c. don't "
            },
            {
                "question": "Woman: ________ did you get home last night?<br>Man: I got a taxi.",
                "options": [" a. What ", " b. When ", " c. Where ", " d. How "],
                "answer": " b. When "
            },
            {
                "question": "Man: Are ________ any bananas on the table?<br>Woman: I'm sorry. I ate the last one.",
                "options": [" a. they ", " b. this ", " c. it ", " d. there "],
                "answer": " d. there "
            },
            {
                "question": "Woman: Please talk on your phone in this area, sir.<br>Man: I'm sorry. I will go outside.",
                "options": [" a. No ", " b. not ", " c. isn't ", " d. don't "],
                "answer": " b. not "
            },
            {
                "question": "Man: Where did you go on vacation?<br>Woman: We went to Florida, and we ________ a great time.",
                "options": [" a. did ", " b. had ", " c. took ", " d. made "],
                "answer": " b. had "
            },
            {
                "question": "Man: Whose is that fantastic car?<br>Woman: Actually, it's ________.\nMan: Lucky you.",
                "options": [" a. theirs ", " b. mine ", " c. yours ", " d. hers "],
                "answer": " b. mine "
            },
            {
                "question": "Woman: I'll be back in the office early on Monday.<br>Man: Right. ________ a good weekend, then.",
                "options": [" a. get ", " b. have ", " c. take ", " d. make "],
                "answer": " b. have "
            },
            {
                "question": "Woman: Sorry I didn't make it to the party.\nMan: What happened?<br>Woman: Oh, I ________ really ill so I couldn't go.",
                "options": [" a. feel ", " b. felt ", " c. feels ", " d. feeling "],
                "answer": " b. felt "
            },
            {
                "question": "Man: Are you looking forward ________ your holiday next week?<br>Woman: Yes, I can't wait.",
                "options": [" a. in ", " b. to ", " c. at ", " d. for "],
                "answer": " b. to "
            },
            {
                "question": "Man: Whose is that money on the table?<br>Woman: It's ________ forgot that I left it there last night.",
                "options": [" a. his ", " b. mine ", " c. ours ", " d. yours "],
                "answer": " b. mine "
            },
            {
                "question": "Man: Do you know Teresa?<br>Woman: Yes, I met her a couple of months _____.",
                "options": [" a. ago ", " b. past ", " c. away ","d. since"],
                "answer": " a. ago "
            }
            
        ]
        
    
    

